We'll be right back.
Scramble over Robin, a cunning plan by Sniper King.
I'll give you three seconds to run for your life.
Three.
Run for my life?
Run from who?
Two.
What?
Stop kidding around, okay?
It's not funny.
And one.
No!
Don't do it!
Chase!
You're nothing more than an incompetent piece of trash.
You call yourself CP9?
Don't make me laugh.
You have to master all six powers to be one of us, rookie.
Califa.
Yes?
On our official report state, the new guy was too weak.
He was therefore deemed worthless.
Understood.
And these are the agents of justice?
Can't tell which side's evil, huh?
Huh?
Just like all the other government officials, you have some extremely bad manners.
Just doing my job.
Huh?
Ha ha ha ha!
Aha!
I knew it!
My intuitive sense of smell has never let me down!
Enough of this nonsense!
Take off that cloak!
Do it!
Damn it!
This is it!
Ha ha!
Wait!
Hold on!
My name is Sniper King.
I'm the mysterious hero from Sniper Island.
You got that?
Sniper King?
Then let's settle down here.
You don't think you're going to get away with this, do you?
Actually, I do.
You should never underestimate a man who is willing to go the distance.
Lucci, help!
I suppose there's no need to ask what you're doing on this train, intruder.
Judging by the way you opened the door, I know exactly the kind of impatient people we're dealing with.
Yeah.
Guess you'll have to excuse my manners.
You've come to rescue Nico Robin?
That is a mistake.
Huh?
Listen.
Her problem is one that's beyond your comprehension.
You see, there are some people in this world who were just born under a bad sign.
People who are, for the sake of everyone else, better off dead.
What are you talking about?
For example...
Suppose there exists a sleeping devil.
One that's capable of burning the entire world to the ground.
And what if there was someone with the ability to wake that devil?
Even if this someone happened to be an eight-year-old girl.
Don't you think that for the lives of every other living being on this planet, that girl should be put to death?
Stop rambling and get to the point.
What I just told you is the true story of Nico Robin.
Her very first transgression.
And now she's accumulated an entire life of crime.
As far back as she can remember, her very existence has been nothing but a sin.
The only good she can do this world would be to forfeit her life and disappear forever.
That's the misfortune she carries with her.
She's cursed.
She has no choice but to accept her fate and die.
Honestly, she should have died over 20 years ago.
We're merely correcting a wrong from the past.
It'll be better for everyone else.
When this is over and she's dead.
Hey!
That's enough!
Bastard!
I don't want to hear another word out of you!
Pity.
Her death won't come nearly as quickly as I would like.
Interrogations.
Torture.
Slowly.
Repeatedly.
The world government is going to keep her alive for years.
Squeezing out all of her knowledge, experiences, and intelligence.
Feel no agony before she...
I'm not gonna let that happen!
Wait!
Robin!
Please don't go in there!
No!
Seriously!
That's a really, really, really bad idea!
Stop!
I said wait!
Not keep going!
Robin!
There you are!
We're in deep trouble.
I'm so happy!
Are you okay?
Say something!
Why are you doing this?
I went through all that trouble to sneak in from the outside!
I even took out that Snoopy government guy!
So that's Nico Robin, huh?
I'd buy that.
Looks like the girl in the wanted poster, that's for sure.
Let me knock these guys out!
Then we'll escape!
We'll run away together and leave all this behind us!
Kay?
It's gonna be alright!
You should talk to me!
I'll jump in!
It's gonna be alright!
You must be alright!
I can't leave that to the inside!
I'll jump in!
Stop!
Robin!
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
It seems that my words mean nothing to you people!
Robin, what are you doing?
It seems that my words mean nothing to you people.
Frankie, quick!
Detach the third car!
Why? What are we gonna do?
Run!
We're gonna run?
What the heck are you talking about?
You too, Sanji. Get ready. This will all be over in a flash.
Make sure that Frankie doesn't escape.
Right.
Sniper King!
Smoke star!
What kind of a stupid stunt is that?
Come on!
I've got her! Move it!
Put me down! Let go!
All right! Run!
Whoa! Turn back!
What was that? He wants us to turn back?
Is that so? Well, that's certainly a relief!
Right. I suppose we should get ready to turn this thing around then.
Nope!
Huh?
Whoa!
But we've already come so far!
No way! What about Robin and Usopp, Zoro?
What are we gonna do? What are we gonna do? What are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do?
That idiot! What in the hell is he thinking?
Hey, Straw Hat! Why do you want her back?
Answer us!
Yeah! Tell us why! You better give us a reason!
That's not what I meant!
Huh?
I was telling that giant frog that jumped on the railway to turn back!
He came out a new way!
It's Yokozuna!
Yokozuna?
No way! Look out! A giant frog's on the tracks!
Froggy! Turn back! Get out of the way!
Shut up!
Look out!
Yes! We did it! We got Robin back!
You know, I should be happy, but I'm not really a big fan of this running away stuff.
That smoke screen was such a stupid idea that it actually surprised them.
Sniper King says,
The plan that involves us not fighting scary guys like them is the best plan of all!
Doubtful.
Besides, that was too easy.
Yeah, these guys aren't like the others. We shouldn't let our guard down just yet.
What's that?
Those thorny whips again?
I've got them.
Now, Luno.
Right.
Quick, cut those things!
Mr.
was reprocess.
I'll come over and get some three guys at one of those.
Basically, boys.
They're new, boys.
Children dei
Music
I'll see you next time.
Stop it! Let her go! Robin, say something!
Robin, you're hiding something, aren't you?
That's fine. Have it your way.
But remember, a pirate can't leave their crew without the captain's permission.
So believe in him. Believe in Luffy.
On the next Wood Piece, the Judicial Island, full view of Eni's lobby, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Thank you.